<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lizah Reyes</title>
    <description>Hi, welcome to lizahreyes.com!  Feel free to browse around each link in the navigation bar and send me a message!
</description>
    <link>lizahreyes.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="lizahreyes.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 00:15:28 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 00:15:28 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>2016 DC Internship Packages </title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This week has been amazingly stressful to say the least.  To sum it up quickly, the 2016 DC internship application packages have just come out and it has all upper year nutrition students on edge.  The School of Nutrition at Ryerson is being super supportive in providing workshops, and I am regretfully reflecting back on this time last year.  Where was I and why was I not attending the workshops?  Either way, time is my only enemy at this point so wish me luck!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 05:51:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>lizahreyes.com/blog/2015/10/07/dc-internship-packages.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">lizahreyes.com/blog/2015/10/07/dc-internship-packages.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>School &amp; work &amp; volunteering..</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This week I had the pleasure of volunteering at a large community event where multiple organizations had showcased the programs that were available to their community members.  I worked at Unison’s Diabetes Prevention Program (DPP) booth to share diabetes-related information and to assist individuals in determining their risk for developing diabetes.  It is a great feeling to share my knowledge with others who aren’t well-versed in this area, to give them the information that they need to make informed decisions about food and nutrition.&lt;br /&gt;
In addition, I got to meet a new volunteer that I coincidentally already work with.  What a great way to end my week, with a new friend!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 05:51:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>lizahreyes.com/blog/2015/10/02/School-work-volunteering.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">lizahreyes.com/blog/2015/10/02/School-work-volunteering.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hi!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting this new school year was very different.  If you didn’t already know, I originally come from Winnipeg, MB (where I grew up!).  After a very good friend of mine moved back home this year, I realized that many of my close friends live in different cities now (Toronto, Winnipeg, Calgary, and in Ann Arbor (Michigan)).  I wanted to share my passion of food &amp;amp; trying new things with these friends, so I started a new mission: recipe food challenge (long-distance).  Every month we choose one recipe to make, and then we all share our experiences of making it + pictures!  Here are the out photos from our first set of recipes:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 05:51:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>lizahreyes.com/blog/2015/09/15/first-blog-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">lizahreyes.com/blog/2015/09/15/first-blog-post.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll-help&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s dedicated Help repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 05:51:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>lizahreyes.com/home/2015/03/15/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">lizahreyes.com/home/2015/03/15/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>home</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
